Guide to the Montana State University Theatre Collection1906-1997
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
Montana State University Theatre records
1906-1997
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
2567
7 linear feet
The MSU Theatre collection consists of materials dealing with specific productions, such as scripts, photographs, playbills, advertisements and other documentation. Other materials deal with the history of the general administration of the theatre program or its physical setting on campus.
In the early years of Montana State University, there was no formal degree program in the dramatic arts. The Alpha Psi Omega Society and the Sock and Buskin Club produced multiple plays annually in the first decade of the twentieth century. Eventually, professional development in terms of courses offered, minors, and finally a major being offered at MSC/MSU occured. Theater courses first appeared in the 1958-60 catalog, and theater first appeared as a separate minor (teaching) under the Department of Education in the 1962-1964 catalog. From 1962-1971 it appeared In the College of Letters and Sciences English Department as a Major Option. (Speech and Theatre Arts). In 1972 it became a separate department in L and S with 3 options and continues as a teaching minor in the Department of Education. In 1984 theater switched over to the College of Arts and Architecture with an addition of a "non" teaching minor being offered as well. A separate Media and Theatre Arts Department emerged in 1988 under the MTA option and listed a Motion Picture/Video/Theatre option for a major. By 2005 the teaching minor had ceased and in 2010 the word "theatre" is dropped from the option title and the department becomes the School of Film and Photography. At present courses are still offered as electives, but there are no options or minors still in existence. In the years when the college lacked a formal degree program in the dramatic arts, the students generally worked with a faculty advisor to facilitate the presentations. Alumni of note who were part of the MSU theater program over the years include Chet Huntley, Bill Pullman and Anthony Zerby. The location of the productions varied over time. Students generally put on about three to five plays per year, and a proper theatre and production facility was built in the Strand Union around 1957. In 2005 all production moved to the new state-of-the-art Black Box Theatre on the western side of the campus. Production evolved from simple box sets through advanced staging and lighting and to compact, durable traveling productions that tour for months at a time such as the Shakespeare in the Parks program.
The MSU Theatre collection consists of materials dealing with specific productions, such as scripts, photographs, playbills, advertisements and other documentation. Other materials deal with the history of the general administration of the theatre program or its physical setting on campus. Oversize materials pertaining to specific productions have been gathered in boxes 17-21. The collection is non-exhaustive with about 90% of the productions coming from 1906–1993.
Series 1 Chronological Files 1906-1997
Series 2 Historical and Architectural files
This collection is open for research.
The collection was assembled beginning in 2010 when a large, disorganized collection of MSU theatre ephemera was given to David Swingle (class of 65) to be sorted and organized into a workable archive that was worth preserving for future research on the MSU's theatre arts history. After a creating preliminary arrangement and inventory, Swingle donated the material to the MSU Library in 2014.
Montana; Montana; Montana
Theater
Colleges and Universities; Performing Arts; Bozeman; Photographs
Photographs; Photographs
- Chronological Files, 1906-1997; 1
  Research materials arranged by date and Production name. They may include brief histories, scripts, programs, brochures, pamphlets, newspaper clippings; news releases; photocopies; slides, photographs and photocopied photographs, and playbills.
  - 1906-1912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1913-1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1925-1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1941-1945 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "The Glass Menagerie", Spring 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Darkness at noon, etc.", Spring 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "The Rain Maker", Spring 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "One Acts" or maybe "Rainmaker" rehearsal, Spring 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "The Solid Gold Cadillac", Spring 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "The Male Animal", Summer 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "My Sister Ellen", Fall 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Blithe Spirit, Fall 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Emperor Jones", Spring 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "The Chalk Garden", Summer 1958 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Old Four Eyes", Summer 1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Four Poster", Summer 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Medea", Fall 1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "The Four Poster", Fall 1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Tobias and the Angel", Winter 1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Death of a Salesman", Winter 1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Ondine", Spring 1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Minstrel Show", Spring 1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Picnic", Summer 1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Tea and Sympathy", Summer 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Bell, Book and Candle", Summer 1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "The Glass Menagerie", Summer 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "Bus Stop", Summer 1959; Fall 1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "Bus Stop" College Cast, Fall 1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "The Apostate", Fall 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "Amahl and The Night Visitors", Winter 1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - "Inherit the Wind", Winter 1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "Biggest Thief in Town", Spring 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Aladdin and His Wonderful Lamp", Spring 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Anastasia", Summer 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer", Summer 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Three Blind Mice", Fall 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "The Crucible", Fall 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "A Streetcar Named Desire", Winter 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Home of the Brave", Winter 1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "The Rivalry", Winter 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Winterset", Spring 1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Simple Simon", Spring 1961 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "The Bad Seed", Summer 1961 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
  - "Janus", Summer 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "Antigone", Fall 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "King of Hearts", Fall 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "The Cave Dwellers", Spring 1961 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "A Season for Crying", Spring 1962 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "Critic's Choice", Summer 1962 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "Let 'Em Eat Steak", Fall 1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Boris Gudenov", Fall 1962 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "Adding Machine", Fall 1962 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "Three Men on a Horse USO tour, Winter 1962 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "Rumpelstiltskin", Winter 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "The Delinquent, the Hipster and the Square", Winter 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "John Brown's Body", Winter 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Slides, Summer 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "The Princess Who Married a Frog", Fall 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Slides, Fall 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "The Adding Machine", Fall 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "The Torch Bearer", Fall 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - One Acts "The Torchbearer" and "Night of the Auk", Fall 1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Rumpelstiltskin, Winter 1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "The Old Maid and The Thief", Spring 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Secret of Suzanne", Spring 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "Singer's Theatre", Spring 1964 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Little Marry Sunshine", Spring 1964 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Thunder Carnival", Summer 1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "Paint Your Wagon", Summer 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "The Man", Summer 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "Arsenic and Old Lace", Fall 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Oedipus", Fall 1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "Waiting for Godot", Winter 1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "The Desk Set", Winter 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "The Birds", Fall 1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Cosi fan Tutti", Fall 1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - "A Christmas Carol", Fall 1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Alice in Wonderland", Winter 1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "Twelfth Night", Winter 1965 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Irma la Douce", Spring 1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "The Canterbury Tales", Spring 1965 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "And People All Around", Fall 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "The Days Between", Winter 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Tenth Man", Winter 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "The Tempest", Winter 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "Roar of the Greasepaint", Spring 1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Gallows Humor", Spring 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Ali Baba", Spring 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "Pajama Game", Spring 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - One Acts "Public Eye" and "Private Ear", Spring 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Under Milkwood", Summer 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "A Thousand Clowns", Summer 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "Absence of a Cello", Summer 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Bernardine", Fall 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "School for Wives", Fall 1967 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "King Lear", Winter 1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Charlie's Aunt", Winter 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "Who'll Save the Plowbox", Winter 1967 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "The Physicist", Winter 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "No Exit", Spring 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - "Most Mad and Moony", Spring 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "Figaro", Spring 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - "Simple Simon", Spring 1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "The House of Bernarda Alba", Summer 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Prometheus", Fall 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - "Desire Under the Elms, Fall 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - "Desire Under the Elms, Fall 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Animal Farm", Winter 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Simple Simon", Winter 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - "Luv", Winter 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "The Killing of Sister George", Winter 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "I was Dancing", Winter 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Champagne Complex", Winter 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "Kiss Me Kate", Spring 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
  - "Walls of a Place", Spring 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5-10)
  - "The Fantastics", Summer 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Romanoff and Juliet", Fall 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "A Message from Cougar", Fall 1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "The Summertree", Winter 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - "Exit the King", Spring 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - "Antigone", Spring 1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - "The Underpants", Summer 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - "The Star Spangled Girl", Summer 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - "The Doll's House", Summer 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - "Don't Drink the Water", Summer 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - "Macbeth", Fall 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Carmen", Winter 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "The Apple Tree", Winter 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
  - "The Lover" (Shoestring), Winter 1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "The Tiger" (Shoestring), Winter 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - "A Flea in Her Ear", Spring 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "Loot", Spring 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Loft Barn Pictures, Summer 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "The Tender Trap" Loft, Summer 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "My Three Angels" Loft, Summer 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "The Only Man in Town" Loft, Summer 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "I Do! I Do!" Loft, Summer 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - "The Caucasian Chalk Circle", Fall 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - "Who's Afraid of Virginia Wolfe?", Fall 1971 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "The Price", Fall 1971 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - "The Princess Who Married a Frog", Fall 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - "Little Murders", Winter of 1971 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - "The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail", Winter of 1971 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "The Man of La Mancha", Winter of 1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - "Scratch", Winter 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "A Company of Wayward Saints", Winter 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Spoon River Anthology", Winter 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "Look Homeward, Angel", Winter 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "Everyman" (Shoestring Theater), Spring 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "Amphitryon 38, Spring 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "The Balcony", Spring 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "Ubu", Spring 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Gus and Dolls", Spring 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - "Plaza Suite", Summer 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "A Mighty Man is He", Summer 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - "The Entertainer", Summer 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "Harvey", Summer 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "Stop the World! I Want to Get Off!", Summer 1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "Dark of the Moon" Ditto's etc., Fall 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "Biederman and the Fire Bugs", Fall 1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - "Christ in the Concrete City", Fall 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "Dark of the Moon", Fall 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - "You're a Good Man Charlie Brown", Summer 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - "The Importance of Being Ernest", Summer 1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - "The House of Blue Leaves" Publicity, Fall 1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "Jabberwock" Publicity, Fall 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "All the Kings Men", Fall 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Dark of the Moon", Fall 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Jabberwock", Fall 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "The Hostage" Publicity, Winter 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "Hail Scrawduke", Winter 1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "The Company of Wayward Saints", Winter 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Under Milkwood", Winter 1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "The Company of Wayward Saints", Winter 1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "The Little Prince", Winter 1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Zoo Story", Winter 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Celebration", Spring 1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "The Balcony", Spring 1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Miss Reardon Drinks a Little", Summer 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "The Biggest Thief in Town", Summer 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - "Echoes" Richard Nash, Fall 1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - "Indians" Arthur Kopits, Fall 1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - "Indians" Kopits (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - "The Hostage", Winter 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - "Endgame" Publicity, Winter 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - "The Mikado", Winter 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Dinner Theatre, Winter 1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - "Night of the Iguana", Spring 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - "The Insect Comedy", Spring 1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - "Happy Birthday, Wanda June" (Shoestring Production), Spring 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - "The Skin of Our Teeth", Spring 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "A Midsummer Night's Dream", Spring 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Moon Children", Fall 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Veronica's Room", Fall 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Blythe Spirit", Winter 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Dinner Theatre, Winter 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "Hotel Paradiso", Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Red Ryder", Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum", Fall 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - "The Time of Your Life", Winter 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - "Hedda Gabler", Winter 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof", Spring 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - "Dracula", Summer 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "The Court Martial of George Armstrong Custer", Fall 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Beggar's Opera", Fall 1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "King Lear", Fall 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - "A La Carte Vaudeville", Summer 1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - "I Do! I Do!", Summer 1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "Mildred Wild" Program, Fall 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - "She Stoops" Program, Fall 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - "Our Town" Programs Layout, Winter 1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - "Bell, Book and Candle", Winter 1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - "Macbeth" Publicity, Spring 1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - "Macbeth", Spring 1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - "Cabaret", Fall 1980 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - "The Mouse Trap", Fall 1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - "Iphigenia", Fall 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "No Exit", Spring 1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "The Same Difference", Spring 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Shadowbox", Spring 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "Dud", Spring 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Something's Afoot", Fall 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "A Christmas Carol", Fall 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "The Real Inspector Hound" (Shoestring), Winter 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "The Real Inspector Hound", Winter 1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Black Comedy", Winter 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Mad Dog Blues", Winter 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Unlabeled Slides (Dinner Theatre), Winter 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "Don't Drink the Water" (Dinner Theatre), Winter 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "The Real Inspector Hound" (Dinner Theatre), Winter 1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest", Spring 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "The Rainmaker", Spring 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "The Importance of Being Earnest", Fall 1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "White Chicks", Fall 1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "The Mad Woman of Chaillot", Winter 1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - "Oklahoma!", Winter 1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - "The Elephant Man", Spring 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "The Apple Tree", Spring 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "The Music Man", Spring 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "A Streetcar Named Desire", Fall 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Walt of the Toreadors", Winter 1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Fiddler on the Roof", Winter 1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Untitled Slides, Winter 1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Laundry and Bourbon", Spring 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Lone Star", Spring 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Damn Yankees", Summer 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Hello Dolly", Winter 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "A Midsummer Night's Dream", Spring 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - "Charlie's Aunt", Fall 1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "The Three Penny Opera", Winter 1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "Godspell", Winter 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "The House of Blue Leaves", Spring 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "The Buried Child", Fall 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "A Child's Christmas in Whales", Fall 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Annie Get Your Gun", Winter 1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Of Mice and Men", Fall 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - "The Foreigner", Winter 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - "Noises Off", Spring 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "K2", Spring 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "The Belle of Amherst", Spring 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Three Places in the Mind's Eye", Winter 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Who's Afraid of Virginia Wolf", Winter 1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - "Educating Rita", Spring 1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - "The Wake of Jeremy Foster", Spring 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - "Carmen", Spring 1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "Melophobia", Fall 1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "The Best Christmas Pageant Ever", Fall 1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - "The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas", Spring 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 6 RMS RIV VU – Publicity, Spring 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "The Marriage of Betty and Boo", Fall 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Orphans", Fall 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Equus", Winter 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Hamlet", Spring 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Little Shop of Horrors", Fall 1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Three Sisters", Fall 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "The Glass Menagerie", Winter 1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "The Boys Next Door", Spring 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "The Nerd", Winter 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - "A Christmas Carol", Winter 1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "Inspector Carol", Fall 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Dance Around a Flagpole", Winter 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "As You Like It", Winter 1993 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "No Exit" and "When the Wind Blows", Fall 1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "Cabaret", Fall 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - "Woman in Black", Fall 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - "All in the Timing", Spring 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Historical and Architectural files, 2 (Volume unnumbered binder)
  Photographs, blueprints, memorandums and other material pertaining to the MSU theatre program but not specifically related to any particular production. Also included are production photographs and slides that cannot be positively matched to a particular production.
  - Save the Theater Fund, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ticket Box Schedule (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SUB Theater Seating Plans (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SUB Theater Bids and Alternatives (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - SUB Theater Funds Specifications (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - SUB Theater Estimates and Specs (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Auditorium (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - SUB Theater – Specifications lighting and Rigging (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Work crews and back stage (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Staff/Building photos (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified slides (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified prints (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - OVERSIZED Materials: Arranged by date and Production title
  - Mounted photo prints, 1970's (Box 17)
  - Mounted photo prints, 1970s (Box 18)
  - Mounted photo prints, 1980's; 1990's (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified mounted prints (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Production posters (Box 21)